<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Quote of the day</string>
    <string name="next_button"> Next</string>
    <string name="quote_text_0"> Problem with internet quotes is that you can\'t always depend on their accuracy.</string>
    <string name="quote_author_0">Abraham Lincoln</string>
    <string name="quote_text_1"> Age is not important unless you\'re a cheese.</string>
    <string name="quote_author_1">Helen Hayes</string>
    <string name="quote_text_2"> It always seems impossible until it\'s done.</string>
    <string name="quote_author_2">Nelson Mandela</string>
    <string name="author_fact_0">Abraham Lincoln was the 16th U.S. President and died over 100 years before the internet existed.</string>
    <string name="author_fact_1">Helen Hayes won an Emmy, a Grammy, an Oscar, and a Tony award.</string>
    <string name="author_fact_2">Nelson Mandela was South Africa\'s first democratically elected president. </string>
    <string name="fact_error">Fact missing </string>
    <string name="imageview_description.xml">Inspirational image of mountains or kittens and such. </string>
    //Homework Quotes
    <string name="quote_text_3">You cannot always see the light at the end of a tunnel but if you just keep moving, you will come to a better place</string>
    <string name="quote_author_3">Uncle Iroh from Avatar: The Last Airbender (Voiced by Mako Iwamatsu)</string>
    <string name="author_fact_3"> Part of the reason why Iroh is silent throughout most of Season 3 of The Last Airbender was because the crew was still looking for a new voice actor while filming due to Mako unfortunately passing away from cancer after the crew finished filming season 2. </string>
    <string name="quote_text_4">Everybody always figures the time they live in is the most epic, most important age to end all ages. But tyrants and heroes rise and fall, and historians sort out the pieces</string>
    <string name="quote_author_4">Jolee Bindo from Star Wars Knights of the Old Republic (Voiced by Kevin Michael Richardson)</string>
    <string name="author_fact_4">Jolee Bindo lived  3956 BBY (Before the Battle of Yavin) and was neither a Sith nor a Jedi. Despite most of his teachings being lost by the time of Return of the Jedi his teachings of knowing both sides of the force and attachments ultimately being what saved you from the Dark Side would end up being the key tenets of Luke Skywalker's New Jedi Order. </string>
</resources>